《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
是我干的
It was me.
我把他从我们的脑海中删去了
I erased him from our minds.
我几乎是亲手杀了我弟弟
I as good as murdered my own brother.
这里不是幻影区
This is not the Phantom Zone.
不要觉得这是个监狱  我不是你的敌人
Don't think of this as a prison. I'm not your enemy.
事实上  我认为我们可以互相帮助
In fact, I think we can help each other.
这是奥拉费人
This is an Aurafacian.
一种附在宿主身上的外星生物
This is an alien organism that attaches to a host body.
好  我来把这些收起来
All right. Let's get these down into holding.
我是来暗中调查安德里亚·罗哈斯
I'm here undercover to investigate Andrea Rojas.
两年的报道
Two years' worth of reporting
表明这是一个比阿尔·卡彭更大的犯罪阴谋
that suggests a criminal conspiracy bigger than Al Capone.
如果你被卷入这件事  我永远不会原谅自己
I'd never forgive myself if you got wrapped up in this.
利维坦要来了
Leviathan is coming.
想象一下你  在一天中的任何时间
Imagine you, anytime of the day,
在世界上的任何地点
anywhere in the world,
与你的朋友们在一起
with all your friends.
然后想象一下
Then imagine
你们想到什么就能做什么
that all of you can do anything that comes to mind.
现在  你不需要再靠想象了
Well, you don't have to imagine anymore.
黑曜石之北"共梦"虚拟现实眼镜
Obsidian North's "Collective Dream" VR lenses
现在已在世界范围发售
are now worldwide.
所以你还在等什么
So why are you waiting?
今天就让你的想象成为现实
Make your imagination your reality today.
想象
黑曜石
共梦
太棒了
Brilliant!
谢谢你  威廉  我很为之自豪
Thank you, William. I'm proud of it.
共梦上线剩余时间
所以我想让所有部门
Which is why I want every department
都写关于发售的报道
to be writing about the launch
直到周五产品发售之后
right up until it happens on Friday.
商业  娱乐  体育  政治
Business, entertainment, sports, politics,
将其融入你们的报道之中  仿佛这关系到
work it into your stories as if our financial well-being
我们未来财政的存亡
depended on it.
因为事实如此
Because it does.
-恶心  -双倍恶心
- Gross. - Double gross.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
你们中一个人需要持续更新
One of you needs to start giving continual updates
我们不断增长的销量
on our growing sales.
我们需要加大力度
We need to pump this up.
-交给我吧  -很好
- I'm your man. - Great.
现在开始工作吧
Now let's get to it.
做微博记者已经够糟糕的了
It's bad enough that we have to do journalism-via-tweet.
现在她还想让我们变成广告写手
Now she wants to turn us into ad hacks?
说到写手
Speaking of hacks...
那位普利策奖得主显然很赞同
Joe Pulitzer is certainly all for it.
我之前很确定你能在
I was so sure you were gonna find something
他名下的地址找到些什么
at that address listed in his name.
首先他与杰罗德博士的死有关
First he is linked to the death of Dr. Jarrod,
然后是墨西哥城的某种秘密行动
then to whatever "covert action" Happened in Mexico City.
我不知道  我很难相信这其中没有联系
I don't know, I find it hard it to believe there's no connection.
我知道  我想我们只是在没有联系的地方
I know. I guess we were looking for connections
寻找联系
where there weren't any.
我是说  他只是在错误的时间
I mean, he was just in the wrong place
与杰罗德博士出现在了错误的地点
at the wrong time with Dr. Jarrod,
给我打电话
我们需要谈谈
努南餐厅  3分钟后见
然后去墨西哥城只是为了找墨西哥环球小姐
and then Mexico City was just about the Miss Mexico pageant.
威廉·戴不是杀手  他只是个大混蛋
William Dey's not a murderer. He's just a grade-A jerk.
没错
Ture.
卡拉
努南餐厅  3分钟后见
-卡拉  你好  -凯莉  好啊
- Kara. Hi. - Kelly, hey.
-我正好需要你  -一切都好吗
- You're just who I needed. - Is everything okay?
是  都挺好  我只是
Yeah, it's good. I just...
想要在我们约会纪念日给艾丽克斯买个礼物
I want to get Alex a gift for our date-aversary,
我真的需要些帮助
and I could really use your help--
谢德尔XG-1000摩托头盔
A Schadel XG-1000 motorcycle helmet,
小号  磨砂黑
in small, matte black.
这建议还真是具体
Oh. That is very specific.
毕竟艾丽克斯都分享到P站了
So is Alex's Pinterest page.
你知道吗  遇见艾丽克斯
You know, meeting Alex
是自从我搬来到纳欣诺市之后
is one of the best things that has happened to me
发生在我身上最美好的事情
since moving to National City.
但生命中有你的出现
But having you in the picture...
是一种额外收获
That's been a pretty cool bonus.
相信我  我对你也有同感
Believe me, the feeling is mutual.
你知道吗  我...
But you know what? I, uh...
我已经答应楼上那群记者给他们送咖啡了
I promised all these reporters upstairs a round of coffee.
-如果我不照办他们会造反的  -好吧
- And if I don't get it, there will be a riot. - Okay.
记住  小号磨砂黑
Uh, remember, small matte black.
记住了
Got it.
怎么回事
What's the deal?
我一早上都在给你发短信
I've been texting you all morning.
手机可能会被黑入
Phones can be hacked.
你可能觉得我太过谨慎  但我正试图曝光
Call me overly cautious, but I'm trying to expose
世界上最有权势的家族的犯罪行为
one of the world's most powerful families as criminals.
我给你发短信就是为了这个
That's why I was texting you.
早上好
Morning.
我想出了个能帮忙的办法
I figured out a way I can help.
卡拉
Kara...
你就...
Just...
听我说完  好吗
Hear me out. Okay?
以你的说法  你找到了各种证据
From what you've explained, you have all this evidence
指出罗哈斯是商业间谍幕后首脑
suggesting the Rojases are masters of corporate espionage,
还有一队特工和杀手
and have a team of operatives
任他们差遣
and assassins at their beck and call.
但却没有他们犯罪的直接证据  对吗
But nothing connecting them directly to the crimes. Right?
对  这是个令人沮丧的失败
Yes, it's a frustrating failure.
如果我告诉你
Well, what if I told you
我姐姐在为一个小政...
that my sister works for a small g...
政府部门
Government agency.
他们逮捕了某人
And they just arrested someone
被认为昨天在墨西哥城想要杀害埃琳娜·托雷斯
who they think targeted Elena Torres in Mexico City yesterday.
卡拉  别告诉我你告诉了你姐姐这事
Kara, don't tell me you told your sister about this.
我没告诉她细节  但是现在我们有线索了
I-I didn't tell her details, but now we have a lead.
代价是什么
What's the catch?
两个条件  第一
Two conditions. One...
你必须签署保密协议
You have to sign an NDA saying
保证你不会告诉任何人她在哪里工作
you will never tell anyone where she works.
第二
And, two...
卡拉  我跟你说了你不会想要卷入这个报道
Kara, I told you you don't want any part of this story.
我这么做不是为了报道
I am not in it for the story.
当...
When...
当安德里亚来到凯特科后
When Andrea come to CatCo,
我以为她只是个烂上司和假记者
I thought she was just a bad boss and a hack journalist.
但要是她真的参与了谋杀
But if she really is actually involved in a web of murders,
我不可能坐视不管
I can't walk away from that.
我是为了正义而战
I am in it for the justice.
你独自调查了这么久
You've been going at this solo for so long.
我可以帮上忙
I could be useful.
让我帮忙能有什么坏处
What's the harm in letting me help?
坏处是你可能会受到伤害
The harm is that you could get hurt.
我说的不仅仅是身体上
I'm not just talking physically.
这事让我失去了朋友  家人
This has cost me friends, family.
对这事的痴迷夺走了我两年的人生
It's an obsession that's taken up two years of my life.
我不想让你经历同样的事
And I don't want that to happen to you.
你不需要担心我  我能照顾好自己
You don't have to worry about me. I can take care of myself.
再说
Plus,
你不带上我  交易就取消了
if you don't bring me the offer's off the table.
好吧
Okay.
你赢了  咱们走
You win. Let's go.
测试对象0505  试验开始
Test subject 0505. Trial commencement.
诱导形象为人类形态2257
Image induce to human-form 2257.
开始
Now.
对象已诱导
Subject induced.
准备好追踪
Prep for tracking.
Q波传感器锁定并准备探测枕叶
Q-wave sensors locked and ready to probe occipital lobe.
卢瑟女士  你知道如果这计划顺利进行
Ms. Luthor, you realize if this goes as planned,
我们将能够掌握如何做到
we are about to discover how to do
那些医生  政客
what it is that doctors, politicians,
甚至牧师都没做到的事
even priests have failed to do.
使人类没有能力再伤害彼此
Rendering people incapable of hurting each other.
激活
Activate.
你休想控制我
You cannot touch me.
超 女
第五季 第五集
戴先生
Mr. Dey,
假如你对罗哈斯的怀疑有一半是真的
if half your suspicions about the Rojases are true,
那这就是巨大的安全风险
then this presents a huge security risk.
不过你只是来旁观的
Still, you are here as observers
所以要听从我的指挥
so follow my lead.
-当然  -让他进去
- Of course. - Let him in.
谢谢你帮忙
Thank you for doing this.
黑曜石全球公司非同小可
Yeah, well, Obsidian Worldwide is a big deal.
再说在黑曜石工作是凯莉的梦想
Plus, working at Obsidian is Kelly's dream job,
所以在我带领超查部去抓她老板前
so before I have the DEO make any moves on her boss,
我得确定她确实有罪
I need to be certain that she is guilty.
是的  说起来
Right, yes. Speaking of, uh,
凯莉之前问我约会纪念日该送你什么礼物
Kelly asked me what to get you for your date-aversary.
她不必送我礼物的
She doesn't need to get me--
我告诉她买谢德尔XG-1000摩托头盔
I told her the Schadel XG-1000 motorcycle helmet
小号  磨砂黑
in small, matte black.
老天  我爱死你了
God, I love you.
这是某种刑具吗
Is this some sort of torture device?
是求真者
It's a Truth Seeker.
它能让想说谎的人无法说谎
It makes it so that those who are inclined to lie, can't.
例如
For example,
是安德里亚·罗哈斯
did Andrea Rojas
雇你袭击埃琳娜·托雷斯吗
hire you to target Elena Torres?
我从不问雇主是谁
I don't ask who hires me.
我的工作在加密的服务器上发布
My jobs come over an encrypted server
以比特币的形式付款
that compensates me in Bitcoin.
你有没有见过安德里亚·罗哈斯
Have you ever met Andrea Rojas
或罗哈斯家族的任何人
or any member of the Rojas family
或任何与他们家族有往来的人
or anyone that they are affiliated with?
我只见过其他接任务的人
I only meet the other contractors.
有个纹身能杀人的女士
There was this lady with killer tattoos,
一个能让好几根手指分离的人
a guy who could detach most of his fingers,
和一个不止两只手臂的壮汉
and this big dude with some extra appendages.
-有几只  -有几只
- How many-- - Howany...
几只手臂
...appendages?
他有四只手臂
He had four arms.
像这样吗
Like this?
是的  就是他
Yeah, that's him.
他的代号名是"嘶吼"
His code name is Rip Roar.
-你上次见他是什么时候  -威廉
- When did you last see him? - William.
-两年前达连湾的任务中见过  -之后没有吗
- Two years ago on a job in Darien... - No time after?
-没有  -戴先生
- No. -Mr. Dey...
那他的老巢在哪  他的目标是谁
So where is he based? Who are his target?
你肯定知道点什么
You have to know something.
我知道的都告诉你了
I have literally told you everything.
你说谎
That's a bloody lie!
-够了  -威廉
-That will be enough! -William.
出去
Out!
你刚才是怎么回事
What was that about?
-你必须告诉我  -他杀了我最好的朋友
-You have to tell me. -He murdered my best friend.
什么
What?
我的大学挚友  罗素·罗杰斯
My mate from college. Russell Rogers.
两年前  他开始怀疑罗哈斯家族
Two years ago, he got suspicious of the Rojases,
第二天  那个怪物就杀了他
and the next day, that monster killed him.
-至今没找到尸体  -那你怎么知道他死了
- Never found the body. - Then how do you know he's dead?
这些都是专业杀手  不会留下证据的
These are professional killers. They don't leave evidence.
我有个朋友能帮忙调查这件事
I have a friend that could help with this.
我根本不该告诉你这些
I should have never told you any of this.
现在你越陷越深了
Now look how involved you are.
所以我才叫你别插手
It's why I told you to stay away.
这是情感的深渊
It's an emotional abyss.
峰脑堡  军事基地
不许动  放下箱子
Hold it. Set the case down.
转过身来
Turn around.
举起双手
Show me your hands.
罗素·罗杰斯
Russell Rogers.
-我会调查他失踪的事  -谢谢你
- I'll look into his disappearance. - Thank you.
你感觉如何
And how are you feeling?
经历了马拉的这么多事
With everything that happened with Mal...
我还在消化整件事情
Well, I'm still processing it all.
但这让我更深地了解自己
But it gave me deeper knowledge about myself and...
和我的族人
And my people.
我能从中学到东西
I can learn from that.
你怎么样  你还好吗
How about you? Are you okay?
你经历了许多
You've been through a lot.
你讨厌的记者原来是好人
The reporter you hated turns out to be a good guy
安德里亚·罗哈斯可能与多起凶杀案有关
and Andrea Rojas is potentially involved in murders.
是啊  除了你和艾丽克斯我不能告诉任何人
Yeah, I can't talk about this with anyone but you and Alex.
我对威廉发誓我会保密
I swore to William I'd keep it secret.
甚至不能告诉尼娅
Even from Nia.
但说实话  我心烦意乱
But honestly, I... I'm, I'm reeling.
我永远不会想到安德里亚是罪犯
I never would have thought Andrea was a criminal
我之前还很确信威廉是坏人
and I was convinced William was evil.
我对他们俩的看法怎么错得如此离谱
How could I have been so wrong about both of them?
现在  到处都是黑曜石的科技
And now, with Obsidian tech everywhere,
所有人都陷在虚拟世界中
I mean, everyone's just in these make-believe worlds and...
如今很难搞清什么才是真的
It's hard to know what's real anymore.
我只希望能更确定
I just want some certainty.
马拉法克的事给我的最大教训就是
You know, my biggest takeaway from what happened with Malefic,
当世界充满不确定性
is when the world is uncertain,
有一样东西坚如磐石
there's one thing that's rock solid.
就是爱你的人
It's the people who love you.
艾丽克斯叫我回超查部
Alex needs me at the DEO.
有人闯入峰脑堡
We had a break-in at Fort Summit.
拜托别告诉我是莱克斯的保险库
Please don't tell me it is Lex's vault.
正确  这就是袭击者
Indeed. And this is the assailant.
就是威廉提到的那个人
It is the same guy William talked about.
他偷了什么
What did he steal?
卢瑟先生称之为马拉松激光束
Mr. Luthor called it his Marathon Laser.
它能发射一道集中热能
It's able to launch a concentrated beam of heat
最远能瞄准42千米外的目标
at a target up to 26.2 miles away.
是杀手的理想武器
It's an assassin's dream.
我们有办法追踪它吗
Is there any way we can track it?
我们正在扫描武器
We are scanning for the weapon.
幸运的话  也能帮我们追踪到那人
With any luck, that will lead us to the man as well.
威廉说
William said
嘶吼是罗哈斯的杀手小队成员之一
Rip Roar was a part of the Rojases's team of operatives.
现在他们在安德里亚的眼镜上线前一天
Now they're stealing one of Lex's weapons
去偷莱克斯的武器
the day before the launch of Andrea's lenses?
假如威廉·戴没怀疑错安德里亚·罗哈斯
If William Dey is right about Andrea Rojas,
两件事之间很可能有关联
there's a high probability of a connection.
但凯莉说虚拟现实设备的发布也是虚拟的
But Kelly did say the VR launch is virtual.
所以人们不会聚集在一处
So people aren't gonna be gathering in one place.
那这武器是用来做什么的
So what use is that weapon then?
我们肯定忽略了什么
We've gotta be missing something.
我再去审问窒息者
I'll take another run at Breathtaker.
不  我们审问过了
No, we tried that.
就算戴上求真者  也什么都问不出来
Even with the Truth Seeker, she's got nothing.
我或许有办法
I might have a solution.
我们不是还抓到了另一个杀手吗
There is always the other assassin we caught.
谁  奥康纳
What, O'Connor?
-她死了  -是的
- She's dead. - Yes.
但她的纹身还活着  有自主意识
But her tattoos are alive and sentient.
我们不需要宿主吗
Wouldn't we need a host?
是的  需要
We would, yes.
在我醒着的时候来找我
Approaching me while I'm still conscious.
你真体贴
How thoughtful of you.
看来我们对彼此的第一印象不太好
It seems we have gotten off on the wrong foot.
所以我有个提议
So I have a proposition.
你有能力在人们脑中植入想法
You have the ability to incept thoughts into people's minds.
我想研究你的大脑
I want to study your brain,
以开发有相同能力的科技
so I can develop a technology that can do the same thing.
原谅我的疑心
Forgive my skepticism,
但上次有人对我的大脑感兴趣时
but last time someone showed interest in my brain,
高级议会将我流放到了幻影区
the High Council sent me to the Phantom Zone.
如果不是因为我  你早就回到幻影区了
You'd be back in the Phantom Zone if it wasn't for me.
然而  我们陷入了僵局
And yet, now we are at an impasse.
我有什么好处
What's in it for me?
我们俩目标一致
We both want the same thing.
都遭到最亲近之人的背叛
We were each betrayed by the people closest to us.
跟我合作
Work with me.
我相信你有能力做大事
I believe you've the ability to do great things.
我不想做大事
I don't want to do great things.
我要复仇
I want revenge.
所以我有一个提议
So I have a proposal for you.
火星生物的思维不允许兄弟间互相伤害
Martian biology prevents a brother from harming his brother.
所以我一直在伤害和荣恩·荣兹亲近的人
That's why I've been attacking the people closest to J'onn J'onzz.
如果你把我脑里的防护罩移除
If you remove this barrier from my brain
好让我杀死我哥哥
so I can kill my brother,
我会让你进入我的大脑
I will give you access to my mind.
如果我的任务是阻止人们互相残杀
It is my mission to stop people from hurting each other.
那我不会杀人
I will not kill.
也许吧
Perhaps.
但是你用极端的手段把我带来这里
But you've gone to extreme measures to bring me here.
你现在站在悬崖边缘
And now, you are at the precipice.
研究我的大脑才是关键
Studying my mind is the key.
我知道绝望的滋味  人类
I know of desperation, human.
我知道你内心深处的感受
I know the depths you feel.
我必须得发明那项技术才行
I would have to develop the technology first.
我接受你的条件
Your terms are acceptable.
开始吧
Let's begin.
我们来说明一下
Okay, so let me get this straight.
只要我们说暗号
Once we say "The phrase,"
你就能增强你大脑的执行部分
you're gonna augment the executive section of your brain
让奥拉费人透过你来说话
to allow the Aurafacian to speak through you.
是的
Yes.
多亏我的测谎仪
And thanks to my polygraph filter,
它就不能说谎
it won't be able to lie.
就是这句暗号
That is the phrase.
我保密了一整天
I've kept it top secret all day.
不客气
You're welcome.
不是吧
Seriously?
这是基努·里维斯的作品
It's from the oeuvre of Mr. Keanu Reeves.
小测试  高手
"Pop quiz, hotshot."
布莱尼
Brainy?
快放开我  人类
Release me, human!
你知道我们是不会释放你的
You know that we're not going to do that.
我们要情报
We want information.
走近点  我就告诉你们
Come near, I'll give it to you.
你和一个叫嘶吼的契约者合作
You worked with a contractor named Rip Roar.
他有一件非常危险的武器
He has a very dangerous weapon.
我们要怎么找到他
How do we find him?
不如在报纸上等个四臂畸形人的广告吧
Perhaps put an ad in the paper for a four-armed freak.
他明天有可能会用这件武器
There's a chance he might use this weapon tomorrow.
你知道他的目标会是谁吗
Do you have any idea who the target might be?
我根本不知道幕后黑手是谁
I never know who's behind it.
我只知道
All I know
有人耗费巨资
is that someone is spending a great deal of capital...
来制造巨大的破坏
to do a great deal of damage.
你已经犯下了几十起谋杀案
You've committed dozens of murders
但你却不知道始作俑者是谁
but don't have the slightest idea who's responsible?
我根本不想知道
I don't care to know.
我根本不在乎你杀死的那些人吗
You don't care about all those people you killed?
他们的家人  朋友
Their family, their friends,
被你杀死的那些人
all those lives you've destroyed?
-你肯定知道些什么  -我不知道
- You have to know something! - I don't know.
不  你知道  我们...
No, you know something and we're--
是布莱尼
Hey, it's Brainy.
氪星人
Kryptonia.
过来  让我把自己印在你的皮肤上
Come here! Let me print myself on your skin!
小测试  高手
Pop quiz, hotshot!
有用吗
Did it work?
我知道  我知道  对不起
I know. I know. I'm sorry.
-我反映过激了  -不  你说得对
- I overreacted. - No. You're right.
这件事比我们想象的还要严重
This is getting way bigger than we thought.
我要去找安德里亚对质
I'm gonna confront Andrea.
先别急
Okay, slow down.
我们要想一个对策
We need to be strategic.
我们要看到事情更重要的一面
Okay? We need to see the bigger plan here.
而且  还有可能她根本都没参与
Plus, there is still a chance that she's not even involved.
你为什么这么说
What makes you say that?
凯莉相信安德里亚  还有她的研究
Kelly believes in Andrea, and the work that she's doing.
那能帮到人
It helps people.
安德里亚从未被指控有任何违法行为
And Andrea's never even been accused of anything illegal.
甚至据威尔说
Even according to Will,
埃琳娜·托雷斯只提供了对她不利的间接证据
Elena Torres offered only circumstantial evidence against her.
凯莉受到了惩罚
Look, Kelly has been through the ringer.
除非迫不得已  我真的不想
And I really don't want to pull the rug out from under her
拆穿她
unless I have to.
相信我
Trust me,
我也想要答案
I want answers too,
但这些指控不小
but these are big accusations
我们需要确定
and we need to be certain.
我知道你的话不无道理
I know everything you're saying makes sense,
但我有这种直觉
but I have this gut feeling
安德里亚在计划一件大事
that Andrea's up to something big.
莱克斯·卢瑟曾经有一个统治世界的计划
Lex Luthor had a plan for world domination
感觉和这个非常类似
that felt a lot like this.
那次  我差点来不及阻止
And that time, I was almost too late.
我不能再让这种事发生
I cannot let that happen again.
我们不会的
We won't.
如果安德里亚和此事有关  我们要查出原因
If Andrea's involved, we'll figure out how.
我有个想法
I have an idea.
超女
Supergirl.
我也相信你的直觉
I trust your gut, too.
马拉松激光束在我这里
I have the Marathon Laser.
你想我怎么用
What do you want me to do with it?
做莱克斯·卢瑟做不到的事
Do what Lex Luthor failed to do.
改变这个世界
Change the world.
凯特科全球媒体公司
明天是个大日子  威廉
Big day tomorrow, William.
五千万订阅用户的大日子
Five million subscribers big.
而且还在增加
And counting.
这才是我想听到的消息
Now that's the news I wanna hear.
小心点
Careful now.
你要捣鼓的可是我的大脑
That's my brain you're about to play with.
枕叶是产生Q波的位置
The occipital lobe is where the Q-waves are generated.
Q波和海豚发出的声纳一样
Q-waves are projected like sonar from a dolphin.
但是你的波有非常特殊的频率
But your waves are a very special frequency
让你有这种独特的能力
that allows you this unique ability
来控制他人的思想和情绪
to control the thoughts and emotions of others.
这就是我们要分离的频率
This is the frequency we want to isolate.
这种独特的能力
That "Unique ability"
是我一生背负的十字架
has been my cross to bear my whole life.
想想
To think
它可以归结为一个简单的频率
it comes down to something as simple as a frequency...
你只要理解这三个测试对象就可以了
All you have to do is incept these three test subjects.
有达克萨姆天蝎
All right? There's a Daxamite Scorpion,
人族海洋恶魔
a Terran Oceanic Devil,
还有马拉多利·德恩卓斯普
and a Maladorian Dendroasp.
当你向他们投射Q波时
As you project your waves at them,
我们就会一边测量频率
we'll measure the frequency,
一边微调  直到数据说正确为止
fine-tuning as we go, 'til we hit the magic number.
准备好了吗
So, are we ready?
只要最后能杀死荣恩·荣兹
As long as killing J'onn J'onzz is the final result,
"我们"迫不及待
"We" can't wait.
真的非常感谢你带吃的来
I really appreciate you bringing food.
正是我需要的
It's exactly what I needed.
又是一个深夜
It's gonna be another very late night, so...
不是吧  怎么了
Oh, no. What happened?
和平时在超查部一样
You know, just another day at the DEO.
失窃的卢瑟武器
A stolen Luthor weapon
还有超能力刺客阴谋
and a conspiracy of meta-assassins.
如果你想聊聊
Well, I am here for you
随时来找我
if you ever need to talk about anything.
当然
Of course.
你怎么样
How are you?
黑曜石都在忙发布的事
Obsidian is abuzz with the launch,
我的一名病人治疗成功
and I had my first patient success story.
他做噩梦一年多了
Yeah. He was having nightmares for over a year.
用了增强现实治疗法后就不再有了
And with VR therapy, they stopped.
真神奇
That's amazing.
还有
And...
我定了位置庆祝约会纪念日
I made a surprise reservation for our date-aversary.
-在海边  -真的吗
- At the waterfront. - Really?
真好
That's nice.
但你不用为黑曜石发布
But don't you have to be on deck
做准备吗
for the Obsidian launch?
既然是虚拟的  我可以把镜片带上
Well, since it's virtual, I can bring the lenses to dinner,
晚餐的时候可以同时参与虚拟庆祝
and then we can join millions in virtual celebration.
你这话真像是
Okay, now that sounds like
替你老板打的诡异广告
one of your boss's freaky advertisements.
诡异并不代表它就不出色
Just because it's freaky, doesn't mean it's not awesome.
-恭喜  -好
- Well, cheers to that. - Ah.
好
Okay.
-威廉  -卡拉  你疯了吗
- William. - Kara, are you mad?
我要查出安德里亚在搞什么鬼
I'm looking for clues to what Andrea's been up to.
我也是  但被她看见的话肯定会杀了你
Well, I am, too. But if Andrea sees you in here, she'll kill you.
-毫不夸张  -没关系
- And that's not a metaphor. - It's fine.
我  我给摄像头动了手脚
I... I looped the cameras.
我从超查部借了点东西  你在这干什么
I borrowed something from the DEO. What are you doing here?
我一早就该干的事
What I should've done in the first place,
调查事情的源头
gone straight to the source.
多亏了军情八处朋友  现在可以了
Now, thanks to my friends at MI-8, I can.
但你得先知道
But, well, you should know first
超查部有了嘶吼的线索
the DEO got a lead on Rip Roar.
在哪  怎么查到的
Where? How?
就我所知
From what I understand,
他偷了一个强力武器
he's stolen a pretty powerful weapon.
他们担心他会在安德里亚发布时
And they're afraid he's gonna use it
一起使用
in connection with Andrea's launch.
就是说我们只有一天不到的时间
That means we have less than a day
查出来她在干什么
to figure out what she's planning.
你真以为
You really think
安德里亚会把信息留在电脑里
Andrea would leave information on her laptop?
她也算是科技高手
I mean, she's kind of tech savant.
这里肯定有信息的
Oh, there's got to be something in here.
要是有的话  你不觉得应该会在
If there is, don't you think it'd be like,
某个角落
in a nook or cranny
地板地下之类的吗
or under the floor or something.
你查你的  我查我的
You look your way, I'll look mine.
不出所料  她有防火墙
Of course she has a Firewall.
"拒绝访问"
"Access denied?"
我觉得我查到脏钱了
I think I hit pay dirt.
你怎么会查到那里
How did you know to look in there?
猜得准
Lucky guess.
你看她藏在这里的东西
But look what she has stashed in here.
外币  很可疑啊
Foreign currency, I mean, that's pretty shady.
某种链子  还有
Uh, some sort of chain and...
这个
Hello.
这人不是罗素吗
Isn't that Russell?
他们认识吗
Did they know each other?
他们可不止认识
They more than just "knew each other."
至少我上次见罗素的时候
At least according to Russell
是这样的
the last time I saw him.
我太喜欢她了  她就是我要找的人
I'm crazy about her. I think she's the one.
你真是没救了
Man, you are sunk.
差不多
Well, almost.
什么意思  她家很有势力
What do you mean? She comes from a powerful family.
家里事情多得很
You know, there's a lot going on there.
他们刻意地不让我知道
And they make a point about shutting me out.
-什么  他们觉得你不够好吗  -不
- What? They don't think you are good enough? - Nah.
不是
It's not that.
他们像是有秘密
It's more like they got secrets.
什么  死尸之类吗
What, like dead bodies?
你不会被牵扯进什么阴谋里吧
Oi, you're not getting into something dodgy, are you?
我能对付
Nothing I can't handle.
听着叫人不放心啊  罗素
This doesn't sound good, Russ.
我只是不知道这些事有多严重
I just don't know how deep these things go with these people.
但安德里亚和她家人不一样
But Andrea is nothing like her family.
我今晚会向她问清楚
I'll sort it out with her tonight.
明天
Then tomorrow,
我就可以找个时间让她见见我最好的朋友
I can figure out a time when she can finally meet my best friend.
什么  你还没跟她提过我
What, you haven't mentioned me?
你觉得在我们确定关系之前我会让她
If you think I'd let her anywhere near that wicked smile of yours
看见你一脸坏笑的样子吗  真是疯了
before we're settled, you're madder than I thought.
那是我最后一次见他
That was the last I saw of him.
罗素
Russell?
该换个新锁了  朋友
You need a new lock, mate.
停下
Stop!
-罗素在哪  -死了
- Where's Russell? - Dead.
天啊  威廉  太可怕了
Oh, my God, William. That's horrible.
我们出去吧
Let's get out of here.
我重新设置了摄像头
Well, I reset the cameras.
没人会知道我们进过安德里亚办公室
No one will know we were in Andrea's office.
她肯定跟这件事有关联
She has to be involved in this.
嘶吼  罗素
Rip Roar, Russell.
你还记得事情发生时她的反应吗
Do you remember how she reacted when it happened?
她是上亿家产的继承人
She is a billionaire heiress.
我没法接近她
I didn't have access to her.
警察查不到线索
The police couldn't find anything,
就认为他是出城去了
so they just presumed he skipped town.
没有尸体  没有线索
There's no body, no leads.
所以为了找线索
So I tried to find some leads
我就去调查安德里亚和她家人
by researching Andrea and her family.
我知道这个方向是对的
I know I'm on the right track here,
只是还没有证据而已
just haven't been able to prove it.
现在杀罗素的人回来了
And now, with Russ's killer back,
或许我应该直白点问她
maybe it's time I just ask her point blank.
威廉  别开这种玩笑
William, don't even joke about that.
我们  我们得先知道对方的情况
We... We have to be certain of what we're up against first.
现在不能莽撞
Now is not the time to be rash.
你还跟我说这个
Look who's talking.
你先闯进安德里亚办公室的
You broke into Andrea's office before I did.
没错  但你
That's true. But you've...
你已经为此付出了这么多努力
You've dedicated so much of your life to this already.
再多观望一下有什么关系
What's the risk in hanging on just for a little bit longer?
你去追查莱克斯·卢瑟的时候
Is that what you told yourself
也是这么告诉自己的吗
when you were chasing the Lex Luthor story?
慢一点  等一下
To slow down and "hang on?"
是这样的  没错
Actually, yeah, it was.
确实很难
And it was really hard.
但那是因为我知道快要查出真相了
But I did it because I could feel that I was close.
就像我们现在一样
Just like I can feel we are so close right now.
不好意思  我姐姐的电话
That's, uh... Sorry, it's my sister.
亚丽克斯  怎么了
Alex, what's up?
布莱尼查到了马拉松激光束的踪迹
Brainy tracked the signature of the Marathon Laser
在新墨西哥州的索科罗卫星站
to the Socorro Satellite Station in New Mexico.
我们需要超女现在过去
We need Supergirl there now.
我马上到
I'm on my way.
我家里有事
Something came up with my family.
答应我  你暂时不要行动
But just promise me you're not gonna do anything.
索科罗卫星站
嘶吼
Rip Roar.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我也知道你杀了罗素·罗杰斯
And I know you killed Russell Rogers.
你一无所知
You know nothing.
并且无能为力
And you're out of your depth.
亚丽克斯
Alex.
我需要荣恩
I need J'onn.
谢谢你帮了我
Thank you for helping me.
我好多了
I'm feeling a lot better.
你知道的  我一直在
You know I'm always here for you.
我去了罗素·罗杰斯
Hey, look, I tracked down the apartment
在伦敦的公寓
where Russell Rogers lived in London.
我做了精神扫描
I did a psychic sweep.
的确有几年前打斗的痕迹
I did see evidence of a struggle there years ago,
但除此之外就没了
but nothing else.
你是说他还活着
You mean he's still alive?
有可能  我还在找
Possibly. I'm still looking.
嘶吼的情况如何  他刚才拿什么打的我
Where are we on Rip Roar and what did he hit me with?
那个叫作聚合炮
It's called a Fusion Cannon.
至少一百年后叫这个
Or at least it is 100 years from now.
是莱克斯的马拉松激光
It's the result of the ingenious combination
与粒子放大器的巧妙结合
of Lex's Marathon Laser plus a particle amplifier.
嘶吼就是从卫星站偷走了这个
That's what Rip Roar stole from the satellite base.
是的  两种技术结合造就了
Yes, the combined technologies create an energy beam
超越太阳中心热度100倍的能量束
100 times hotter than the center of the sun.
如果能造成这样的损坏
If it's capable of damage like that,
想想它还能做什么
imagine what else it can do.
我们得赶紧找到它
We need to find it.
是啊  说到这个...
Uh, yes, about that...
放大器的放射会模糊聚合炮的能量特征
The amplifier's radiation obfuscates the cannon's energy signature,
因此追踪起来非常困难
which makes tracking it quite difficult.
黑曜石之北发布就在今天
Well, Obsidian North's launch is today.
不管安德里亚在计划什么  也许到头了
So whatever Andrea's been up to, will probably come to a head.
布莱尼  关于发布有什么我们没注意的吗
Brainy, is there anything about the launch we might have missed?
没有
Negative.
距离共梦发布还有
这之间一定有联系
Gotta be connected.
安德里亚  嘶吼  那个武器
Andrea, Rip Roar, the weapon.
在他伤害其他人之前  我们必须查清楚
And we've got to find out how before he hurts anyone else.
必须得阻止他
He's got to be stopped.
凯莉来电
艾丽克斯  是我
Alex, hi, it's me.
我知道你很忙
Look, I know you're busy,
我直接把今晚的餐厅地址发给你
so I will text you the address for the restaurant tonight.
如果你要晚点到也没关系
And if you're running late, don't worry.
按你的计划赶到就行
Just get there when you can.
然后我们一起放松
And we'll start to relax.
好了  各位
Okay, people.
距离共梦发布还有不到一小时
The Collective Dream launch is in less than an hour.
威廉  用户量数据是多少
William, what is our user count?
会有九百万
We'll have nine million.
这比世界上许多国家人口还多
That's more than the population of most of the world's countries.
干得漂亮
Well done.
接下来是最终的测试项目
And now, our final test subject,
马拉多利·德恩卓斯普
the Maladorian Dendroasp.
它的攻击力强于地球上所有武器一百倍
It is 100 times more aggressive than anything on Earth.
拿出你对付他们的实力对付它
I want you to do to it what you did to them.
感应器已校准并准备好
Sensors are ready and calibrated.
动手
Now.
巨蝎 海洋魔鬼
马拉多利·德恩卓斯普
同步  已匹配
满意了吗
Satisfied?
成功了
It worked.
沃斯托克湖
Lake Vostok.
你说英文  布莱尼
Okay, in English, Brainy.
其实  这是在南极洲
Actually, it's in Antarctica,
我认为嘶吼就是想去那里
where I believe Rip Roar is heading.
南极
Antarctica?
通过交叉比对
After cross-referencing information gleaned
窒息者和奥拉费人的相关琐碎信息
from Breathtaker and the Aurafacian,
我发现罗哈斯的三位杀手
I have discovered that each of the three Rojas assassins
都瞄准了同样的目标
all targeted an employee
员工
就是南极站沃斯托克湖的员工
of the Lake Vostok Antarctica Base,
并且刺杀都发生在上个月
all within the last month.
一名科学家  工程师和安保长官
A scientist, an engineer and a security officer?
有什么联系呢
What's the significance?
综合考虑一下每个目标所知的信息
Well, given what each of the targeted individuals knew,
很有可能  那个基站的所有安保程序
it is possible that every single security protocol on that base
已经都可以被重写了
can now be overridden.
我还是不明白
I still don't get it.
沃斯托克湖是世界上最大的冰川湖
Lake Vostok is the largest subglacial lake in the world.
我虽然不是超级反派
Now, I'm no super-villain,
但如果是我
but if I were,
刚好路过南极一座湖
and I was right over an Antarctic lake
手里的武器还能够发布
with a weapon designed to fire a beam 100 times hotter
热度高于太阳中心一百倍的光束
than the center of the sun,
这简直就是所谓的
well, it would be, as they say,
"今晚老城要热闹了"
"a hot time in the old town tonight."
但这不是什么好事
Not that that's a good thing.
你的意思是  他是要融化沃斯托克湖
So you're saying that he's going to melt the ice cap
周围的冰川吗
around Lake Vostok?
如果他这样做
If he did that,
就会造成超过诺亚方舟时代的洪水
it would unleash a flood unseen since the time of Noah's Ark.
沃斯托克湖研究中心
这个还活着
This one's still alive.
嘶吼  不要
Rip Roar, no!
情况如何
Status?
南极水位的极度上升
A massive eruption in the Antarctic water table
给东西方向造成了巨大激波
has sent shock waves east and west,
导致各地区出现前所未有的大海浪
resulting in an unprecedented number of sea swells.
根据海底地形
Based on the seafloor pattern
以及南极洲绕极海流分析
and the Antarctic Circumpolar Current,
最大的海浪在不到一小时后
the biggest is set to make landfall
就会登陆太平洋海岸
on the Pacific coast in under an hour.
太平洋海岸的哪部分
Which part of the Pacific coast?
全部
All of it.
这就走了吗
Leaving so soon?
算你聪明
Smart move.
你做了什么
What have you done?
他们让我做什么就做什么
I do what they tell me to.
他们  他们是谁
They? Who is "they?"
我不知道
I don't know.
超女  你能听到吗
Supergirl, can you hear me?
艾丽克斯  我们找到了嘶吼
Alex, we have Rip Roar,
但他在湖里打了一个孔
but he punched a hole in the lake.
我们知道  那次冲击直接送了海浪过来
We know. The eruption just sent a tidal wave our way.
我们能处理海浪  超女
We can deal with the swell, Supergirl.
你和荣恩得把那个喷水口封起来
You and J'onn need to seal that geyser,
不然我们要处理的就不只是海浪了
or else we'll have bigger problems than a wave.
什么意思
What do you mean?
那里每秒钟都会喷出三立方英里的水
That geyser is pumping out three cubic miles of water every second.
这样的速度下  十二分钟后
At that rate, every coastal city in the world
每座海滨城市都会被淹没
will start flooding in 12 minutes.
可能会有百万人死亡
The loss of life could be in the billions.
我们该怎么阻止海浪
So how do we stop that wave?
梦想者
Dreamer.
来不及了
It's too late.
一旦开始就无法阻止了
Once it's started it can't be stopped.
相信我
Trust me,
我一定能阻止
I can stop this.
谢谢
Thank you.
广告短信
黑曜石
欢迎各位  这一定是诸位人生中
Welcome one and all to the most amazing party
想象
最精彩的派对
you'll ever attend.
欢迎
Welcome,
欢迎来到共梦
welcome to The Communal Dream.
欢迎
Welcome,
欢迎各位
welcome, everyone.
我们得让水流反向
We'll have to invert the flow of water.
喷泉在往上推水
The geyser's pushing it up.
也许旋涡能把它拉下去
Maybe a whirlpool could pull it down.
那我们就绕着基站飞
We'll fly around the base.
但是必须保持完美队形
But we need to do it in perfect formation.
这么大水量
With this amount of water,
吸力可能会把你拉进去  让你窒息
the suction could pull you under and suffocate you.
好  那我们最好稳住身形
Well then, we'd better keep our cool.
你怎么没去参加发布会
Why aren't you at the launch?
你是发现更重要的事了吗
Did you find something more important?
其实
Actually...
我确实有所发现
I did find something.
他叫罗素·罗杰斯
His name is Russell Rogers.
什么
What?
我看到那张照片了  安德里亚
I saw the photo, Andrea.
你们俩的事我全都知道了
I know all about the two of you.
你跟他一起干了什么
What did you do with him?
我不知道你在说些什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我知道奥康纳
I know about O'Connor
窒息者和嘶吼的事情了
and Breathtaker and Rip Roar.
我还知道你和你们家族的内幕
I know about you and your family,
以及你们侥幸逃脱的一切罪行
and everything you've gotten away with.
贪污  盗窃  杀人
Corruption, theft, murder.
但是你们现在逃脱不掉了
But you're not going to get away with it any longer.
因为我要毁了你们
Because I am going to destroy you,
即便这样会搭上我的性命
if it's the last thing I do.
威廉
William...
William?
发布会进展得很顺利  你不觉得吗
The launch is going great, don't you think?
是的  罗哈斯女士
Sure is, Ms. Rojas.
梦想者
Dreamer?
好大的浪啊
That's a huge wave!
布莱尼  但愿这行得通
Brainy, I hope this works.
大家赶紧躲到高处去  快走
Everybody get to high ground! Go!
好了  我帮你  趴下
Right. I got you. Down!
走  大家快转移  转移
Go! Everybody move, move!
行动
Now!
他开口了吗
Did he say anything?
他缄口不言  即便是戴上求真者
He isn't talking. Even with the Truth Seeker.
但他说了"他们"
But he said "they."
"他们"指示他做了那些事
"They" told him to do what he did.
他肯定知道些什么
He has to know something.
但据布莱尼说
But according to Brainy,
他穿戴的科技产品具有生物附着性
I mean, the tech he wears is biologically adhered
它就像某种精神盔甲
and it functions as some sort of mental armor.
我们没法进入他的头脑
We can't get to him.
而且幕后主使不是罗哈斯家族
Also, it wasn't the Rojases.
-什么  -我们进行了分析
- What? - We ran the analytics.
淹没西海岸
Okay, flooding the West Coast
会摧毁黑曜石之北的制造中心
would've taken out Obsidian North's manufacturing hub.
如果你和荣恩没能阻止那道巨浪
And if you and J'onn hadn't stopped the geyser,
他们会损失数十亿
then they would've lost billions.
我想说  幸好我不用告诉凯莉
I gotta say, I'm glad that I don't have to tell Kelly
她的老板是个犯罪头目
that her boss is a crime lord.
但这让我们的案子仍然毫无头绪
But this still leaves us with a case that doesn't make any sense.
如果主使不是安德里亚和罗哈斯家族
If it wasn't Andrea and the Rojases,
那发号施令的是谁
who was calling the shots?
-这件事肯定有幕后黑手  -我同意
- Someone has to be behind this. - I agree.
不管是谁  我们都要找到他们
And whoever it is, we're gonna find them.
只是需要的时间可能比我们想象中要长
It just might take longer than we thought.
我有样东西要给你们俩看
There's something you both should see.
凶猛巨浪威胁海滨区
凯莉  你还好吗
Kelly, you okay?
你一副见了鬼的样子
You look like you've seen a ghost.
是啊
Yeah.
昨天的事情让我...
Yesterday was just, um,
难以承受
a lot.
海滨区发生了危机
With everything that happened at the waterfront.
艾丽克斯表现得很棒
And Alex was... She was amazing.
但我当时在场
But I was there
我几乎眼睁睁看着她送命
and I almost saw her die.
我因此而崩溃了
I guess it triggered me.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我知道艾丽克斯能照顾好自己
Look, I know that Alex can take care of herself.
我很清楚  但是
I do. But...
我的未婚夫死于前线的战斗
My fiancé died fighting on the front lines,
我一直没能跨过这道坎
and I never got over it.
昨天那一幕让我想起了当年的情景
This brought it all back.
我无法摆脱这种...
I just... I can't shake this feeling of...
恐惧感
...dread.
听起来你需要朋友的安慰
Well, it sounds to me like you could use a friend.
你想改天一起吃午餐  谈谈心吗
Do you wanna grab lunch sometime and talk?
我很乐意
I'd like that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
结束了
It is finished.
什么结束了
What is?
你移除了我的思想屏障之后
I have clarity on how to dispose of my brother,
我清楚如何处置我哥哥了
now that you've removed my mental block.
但我并没有移除它
But I didn't remove it.
我绝不能让你伤害其他人
I could never let you hurt another person.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
如果你凭直觉了解过我的研究  你就该知道这点
If you intuited anything about my research, you'd know that.
你喜欢这里  对吧
You like it here, don't you?
是的
Yes.
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
非常喜欢
I like it very much.
你好美
You look beautiful.
我确实穿了你最爱的颜色
Well, I did wear your favorite color.
抱歉我错过了我们的约会纪念日
I'm so sorry that I missed our date-aversary
也没听到你的语音留言
and your voicemail.
但你也知道我们在对抗强敌
But you know what we're up against.
你非常勇敢
You were incredibly brave.
我这些年确实掌握了一些技能
Well, I've developed a few skills over the years.
过来  我给你准备了礼物
Uh, come here. I... I got you something.
我也给你准备了礼物
Oh, I got you something, too,
但我忘带了
but I forgot to bring it.
没关系  今天不是我们真正的约会纪念日
Oh, that's okay. This isn't our real date-aversary.
等到了那天再送我也不迟
So when it is, you can give it to me then.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
-闭上眼睛  -好的
- Close them. - Okay.
好了  睁开眼
Okay, open.
谢德尔XG-1000头盔
A Schadel XG-1000.
这样我就可以骑摩托车载你了
So you can be my riding partner.
太棒了
This is amazing.
我们现在能在一起  我真是太高兴了
I'm just so glad that we can be together right now.
谢谢
Thank you.
别担心
Don't worry.
我没有跟安德里亚对质
I didn't confront Andrea.
不过相信我  我想那么干来着
Though, believe me, I wanted to.
我现在更迷茫了
Now, I'm even more confused than ever.
如果昨天嘶吼得逞了
The Rojases would've lost everything
罗哈斯家族会失去一切
if Rip Roar had succeeded.
如果他们不是坏蛋  那又会是谁呢
If they're not the villains, then who?
现在事情变得更令人难以捉摸了
And now it gets even more confusing.
超查部抓到了嘶吼  并确认了他的身份
The DEO caught Rip Roar and they were able to ID him.
是罗素
It's Russell.
不  什么
No. What?
这  这不可能
That's... That's not possible.
他们不是把他给杀了吗
I thought they killed him.
我做这一切都是为了替他报仇
All of this was to avenge his death.
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
他们是怎么把他变成了那个...
What could they have done to turn him into that...
怪物
monster?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我知道这让你很痛苦
I know how painful this is.
但现在我们已经拘留了他
But now that we have him in custody,
好的方面是
the good thing is
我们终于可以解答你的疑问了
we can finally get you some answers.
关于他  安德里亚
About him, about Andrea,
以及我们可能发现的其他问题
about any other questions we might uncover.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也知道我不希望你牵涉进来
You know I didn't want you involved in this.
但如果没有你  我都不知该怎么做到这些
But I don't know how I would've done it without you.
谢谢
Thank you.
黑曜石隐形眼镜是新的智能手机吗
你推出的隐形眼镜真是太了不起了
You've really outdone yourself with those contact lenses.
我听说它们就像瘟疫或洪水一样
I hear they're as omnipresent as one of our plagues
无所不在
or floods.
昨天那事是你干的吗
That was you yesterday?
利维坦无处不在
Leviathan is everywhere.
现在出现了一个问题
And now a problem has come up.
我们需要你去解决
We need you to fix it.
事关嘶吼
It's Rip Roar.